<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Accessibility 101</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_example">Example action</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <!-- Global Story Strings-->
    <string name="story_tab_title_about">About</string>
    <string name="story_tab_title_broken">Broken</string>
    <string name="story_tab_title_fixed">Fixed</string>

    <!-- Intro Story Strings-->
    <string name="intro_title">Introduction</string>
    <string name="intro_tab_1">About</string>
    <string name="intro_tab_2">Deque</string>

    <string name="intro_about_paragraph1">Welcome to Accessibility 101.  This app will take you through a set of demonstrations that aim to help developers understand the implications the Android Accessibility APIs have for users with disabilities.  Below are a few tips for getting the most out of this application. \n\n - Enable TalkBack\n - Enable TalkBack Shortcut</string>

    <string name="intro_deque_paragraph1">Accessibility is both our mission and our passion and something we have been doing for over ten years with major corporations, government agencies, and other organizations. Every Deque team member – some of whom have been with the company since it was founded in 1999 – is passionate about the importance of accessibility in the digital world and in helping customers achieve the outcomes that accessibility provides. Our culture focuses heavily on these key pillars, in hiring, evaluation, and career paths and we have fostered a team of website accessibility experts.</string>

    <string name="intro_deque_contact_button"><u>Contact Us</u></string>

    <!-- Labels Story Strings-->
    <string name="labels_title">Labels</string>

    <string name="labels_about_heading_1">Labels vs contentDescriptions</string>
    <string name="labels_about_paragraph_1">In the Android Accessibility world there are multiple ways of providing alternate text for a control.  The contentDescription is the most basic.  However, you can also use the labelFor attribute.  By marking a text element as the "labelFor" something, you associate a visible label with the announcement in TalkBack.  While not all controls require a contentDescription, all controls that do not contain text as a primary feature of the control, absolutely require a label of some kind!  Labels are not an Android element, it is a word we have chosen to represent the presence of either a labelFor or a contentDescription.  In general, the labelFor property should be preferred.</string>

    <string name="labels_about_heading_2">Using contentDescriptions</string>

    <string name="labels_about_heading_3">Using labelFor Attribute</string>

    <string name="labels_about_heading_4">Mixing Them Together</string>

    <!-- ContDesc Story Strings-->
    <string name="cont_desc_title">Content Descriptions</string>

<!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

</resources>
